More than a thousand years ago,
China broke into three kingdoms at war.
Food became the paramount necessity.
To feed his soldiers,
one emperor invented 'Mojin Xiaowei'
They are official tomb robbers
borrowing gold from the dead...
for the livings.
They have strict rules to follow:
Before a coffin is opened
a candle must be lit at
the southeast corner
If the candle goes out
the Mojins must return
the treasures and leave the tomb.
Or else there would be catastrophes.
To escape the deadly traps is
no more than a piece of cake...
for the Mojins.
Candles are dimming out.
Leave it!
Wait.
We've been out of business for months!
We can't let this treasure slip!
Hu Bayi!
1988, Mojin Xiaoweis retired
from tomb raiding
and fled to New York
in Shirley's demand.
Hi girl, come on.
Look at me. Look at me.
Chinese treasures!
You see see.
What do you think?
Do you like my babes?
Treasures!
Culture!
Luck!
Good Luck. Really?
Who I am?
Who he is?
We are 'Mojin Xiaowei', you know?
Kung Fu! You know? Kung Fu!
Very Great.
If your Kung Fu's so great
why are you doin' business on the street?
They say America is sick!
Wang
Something's wrong here.
One sec, almost there.
Show me your ID.
What?
This is the INS.
Turn around.
Put your hands behind your back.
Sorry I...I don't know English...
What is your name?
Where are you from?
Hey!
We have ID.
ID!
Ah..ID!
I know I know I know...
Run!!!
This is Officer Durham.
We are chasing two Asian men...
Where to?
To seek the Dragon through obstacles,
each obstacle is a gate
Left to Broadway, right to Central Street.
Up instead of down, left instead of right.
Shut up!
Left or right?
Left!
I knew there was
something wrong with her.
Watch out!
Dragon Seeking doesn't work here.
Go!
Get in !
Yang!
You guys go first
and I take care of the rest.
What?
The rest?
You'd better take care of yourself.
There!
We are the "Mojin Xiaowei".
But here we are chased
on the streets all the time.
What the fuck!
I'd rather be sent back to China
What the hell is this country.
I can't find you anywhere.
Are you hiding from me?
No way.
Why would I hide from you?
Mom told me,
if you have slept with a man
never contact him first.
Wait for him to come to you.
My mom also told me,
If he doesn't
forget about him.
What a cool mom.
You don't need to hide.
Let's just pretend nothing had happened.
Yeah!
That was that I said.
We were so drunk.
I slept with the toilet the whole night.
Ah.
Drunk like that,
You two would have regretted
Whatever you've done.
He's talking about us quitting.
Of course.
What else would I talk about?
A couple of shots down
and we were finished.
We've been raiding all our lives
how can we just quit?
Are you kidding me?
Well,
that's already decided.
period.
How about getting married?
I mean fake marriage.
Then you could get the green card.
And find a proper job...
A Mojin Xiaowei
has to rely on fake
marriage to get a job...
Why not be a hooker?
If the master had known this,
he'd crawl out from the grave
to beat you up.
Stop talking about "Mojin Xiaowei."
We've made the vow to quit
There's no way around
I...I was drunk...
I...I don't remember anything.
I don't.
You irresponsible men!
We gotta be responsible
for our profession first.
He passed the Mojin Amulet
on to us with his expectations.
And here we are.
Grill just got us a big deal.
Let's get back to the business
and leave this 'sick America.'
Yo?
What are you doing.
Hu Bayi!
The wold won't stop because of you.
You
Have a carefully look
These are the treasures from
the tomb of Empress Dowger Cixi.
Mojin Xiaoweis risked their lives
to dig out this pearl out of her mouth.
It absorbed the essence of the nature
to preserve her body from decay.
This pearl's from Chinese
most famous woman's tomb.
Very good.
You are a true expert.
A mediocre piece won't get your attention.
You surely heard of the Emperor of Qin.
The first emperor of China.
His tomb was also raided by the Mojins.
This piece is the greatest among the all.
The Skeleton Mirror.
"...tomb, very very good.
Look who's here!
I would like to proudly present
this gentleman,
who is none other than
the legendary Emperor Weiwu's
eighty-second generation
of Mojin Xiaowei,
the No.one of tombraiders
Mr. Wang Kaixuan.
Where is Mr. Hu?
Fuck that bastard!
Well...
Come and see ! Come come!
Come come!
Look, look.
This is the legendary Mojin Amulet,
The signature of a real Mojin Xiaowei.
Mr. Kai
What's going on?
Come and sit here.
Hello.
I'm the Executive director
of Global Mining Co, Mark.
Miss Yoko is our president's secretary.
Our president Madam Ying Caihong is
very interested in ancient Chinese culture.
She rates highly of
the skills of Mojin Xiaowei.
And is expecting your assistance
regardless of cost.
No.
If so,
I'd say that at least
five...
...hundred thousand dollars.
No problem.
Let's make it a deal.
Here is the information
of the tomb and our contract.
I'll sign the contract.
What contact?
What the hell are you doing?
It's been so many years
Mr. Kai.
Mojins as a team;
United we stand, divided we fall.
Hu Bayi, son of a bitch, has betrayed us!
It doesn't matter if we have money.
So let's do it.
Let me suggest something
for the sake of your sincerity
Another fifty thousand.
What? Thirty thousand?
No way!
You misunderstood.
She means she'll triple your offer.
Far enough for people like you.
Sign the contract then.
Oh Yeah.
Fuck off.
You got money huh ?
Cash or check?
You think you are something?
Fuck you people who think
money can buy everything.
Mr. Kai!
You wanna buy me out with money?
Let me tell you, no bloody way.
I am Wang Kaixuan, Mr. Kai!
Why are you sleeping in the tent?
Weirdo.
According to Fengshui
today
today is not a good day
for trade
or marriage...
Enough!
No one wants to marry you.
I was planning
to see you after I woke up...
and discuss about us...
What about us?
Your attitude already made the conclusion.
You are allowed to regret.
I don't regret it.
So?
Yeah?
So what?
I'm not here to argue with you.
You have something delivered to my place.
Ah.
This is the last time I pick it up for you.
Next time I'll leave it at the door.
You go get it.
Hey...
Take it easy...
If you leave us alone
we'll be in a mess.
Ciao.
Hey!
Just wanna tell you that I'm back to China.
Not because of you.
I don't have time for the argument.
I'm going to check out this tomb
from Liao Dynasty.
It has nothing to do with money,
and I didn't mean to tell you this...
Yeah, right.
But the Equinox flower...
You do remember this flower right?
The special kind of lily
mentioned by Ding appears again.
This time I came back tor Ding.
I need to find out what's going on.
It's up to you to join me or not.
Going back to old business again.
And now he's trying to drag you into this
by sending this inveracious tape.
No.
Wang would never use Ding Sitian
as the bait.
Who's Ding Sitian?
1969, Inner Mongolia, China
Twenty years ago,
Wang and I relocated ourselves
in Inner Mongolia
for 'Up to the Mountains
and Down to the countryside'.
That summer
we marched into the forbidden area led
by the herdsmen,
searching for the thousand year
Goddess tomb, to destroy
the 'Four-olds'.
Ding Sitian was our comrade
her parents were
both renowned botanists.
Ding was talented in music and art.
Thousands of red hearts facing Beijing
Thousands of smiling faces
greeting the red sun
in praise of Long Life for Chairman Mao
Dear Chairman Mao...
Ah!
What's the matter?
You stay put and don't move!
The wheel is stuck!
What should we do?
Don't panic! Everybody push, hurry!
Ding, come.
It's okay. I can to it.
You haven't finished
your flower collection yet right?
Let me know If you are missing
any and I'll find it for you.
Leave all the hard work to Wang,
he can surely handle it.
He can climb up to the moon
and dive down to the ocean.
While we sing and dance on the ground.
I'll stay with you
Hey Hey!
'It's not difficult
to commit some misdeeds.
But it's difficult to commit only misdeeds
and no good deeds,' said Chairman Mao.
He meant exactly you.
Attention!
What happened?
Be alarmed, enemy ahead!
Get your weapons, hurry!
Come and take this!
Go!
Ding,don't worry.
Hey!
Take a look there.
Watch out the mud.
They are enemies?
They're only statues.
More over there!
And here!
There too!
Don't get closer.
Why?
...guarded by the stones...
blessed by the Goddess...
What's he saying?
He says that we've arrived
to the limbo of life and death.
These are the guards of the Underworld.
We must go no further
or else none will return.
You know this shit.
What's going on here?
This area is indeed strange.
Throughout the history
we working class people
would always break
the emperors' tombs for revolutions!
True!
Indeed!
It shows the determinations
against the feudal power!
Hold on, hold on!
Hold on!
The Great Chairman Mao said
All power can be united
must be united, right?
Right!
Look!
These soldiers were
the proletarians of the old days!
Shouldn't we
unite them too?
You got a point.
Bullshit.
All counter-reactionaries
must be abolished.
Excuse us to disturb you...Excuse us...
Only the greatest ambitions
and sacrifice lead to a brave new world!
A brave new world!
Let's destroy the statues!
Destroy them!
Harder!
Through all hardship victory will be ours!
Comrades, this is a
great victory of the people!
Great victory!
Now let's go and destroy
the tomb of the Goddess!
They've gone mad
What's the matter?
Something's wrong.
Hold on.
Attention.
Watch out everybody!
Something's moving underground.
Shut up you superstitious
counterrevolutionary two-faces.
Oh my god...
Get Ding out of there!
Run! This way!
Run! Run!
This way!
Run!
You are all the paper tigers!
Hurry up!
Get down!
Go!
Quickly!
Hurry up!
Ding!
Wang!
Hu, come here!
Go!
Come here quickly!
Here!
Inside!
Cover it!
We've lost so many comrades.
What do we do now?
It's okay.
There's always something.
Stay calm.
Wang! Wang!
Here's a door.
Where is this place?
Be careful.
Follow up!
What the hell is this place?
It's so deep.
Watch out the steps.
Is this the way out?
It's okay...
Where is this place?
It's huge here...
Look around
Find a way out.
Follow me. Don't be afraid.
Okay.
Here's a dead end.
Wang.
It looks like a Japanese
underground military base.
Ah?
Military base?
Tunnel for war.
There. You lead the way,
I bring up the rear.
Power distribution room.
Ammunition depot.
You follow Hu.
Un...underground base...
Hope there's no Japanese here...
Come on. They are all dead.
Don't scare yourself.
I mean...
Dynamite!
This looks like a dumbwaiter.
A dumbwaiter!
We can get out from here!
Yeah!!
Is't still working?
What's this?
Here's another ammunition depot.
Put it out!
Everybody watch out.
There are dynamite attached to
all the structural joints
Once lit up, the entire base will collapse.
Let's just leave one torch for the road.
Hurry up! Put it out!
We'd better think about
how to re-start the dumbwaiter.
Look, here are the wires!
They would lead us
to the power generator.
Let's have a look.
Come on!
It's on!
Yes!
Great!
It's on!
We can get out!
Let's go.
Don't be afraid.
It's okay. It's okay.
You see,
A dried corpse.
It's okay.
God... It's full of corpses.
How come these Japanese died here?
Look they all carry guns.
Statues over there!
We should go back.
Yeah it's dangerous there.
We'd better go back.
Let's go back.
Let's not get ourselves in trouble.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's go.
What are you all afraid of?
We are materialists.
True materialists are fearless.
Take out your little red book.
Quickly!
Take it out!
True materialists are fearless.
Let's smash the "Four olds."
These Japanese all dead in strange ways.
It seems that they found these statues
and tried to move them away.
Then Something happened.
Whatever these 'F our-ems' are,
They are for us proletarians.
Not for the Japanese invaders!
Take it.
For self defense!
Okay.
Don't worry, I'm protecting you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The Equinox flower!
What?
According to the legend, it only
exists at the limbo of Yin and Yang,
and connect the living and the dead.
The Equinox flower?
Yes, I heard the flower's so beautiful.
Yeah?
I really want to see it.
Count it on me!
Really?
I'll find it for you
even it's in hell.
You promise.
There are still many 'Four-olds'
to be destroyed.
Comrades, let's go!
Go!
It's dangerous!
Hold on!
It's huge.
God damn it!
It'll take us forever to destroy them all.
Comrades, let's do it!
Don't!
Stop it!
What's wrong?
The Japanese!
What the hell is that?
Help!
Come down!
Go!
Careful!
Go
Ding!
Get out!
Fuck off!
Hu Bayi!
Let me go.
Ding!
Wang!
Wang Hurry up!
Go!
Damn it!
Run!
It exploded.
The place was turned into a sea of fire.
We ran for our lives,
Ding Sitian and our comrades all died...
Only Wang and myself
managed to escape by the dumbwaiter.
It's been twenty years.
Wang never wanted to bring this up.
At that time we saw the Equinox flower.
I've heard that it's the sign
of Princess Augo from Khitan.
I never expect that
it would appear again.
You said that you witnessed
the corpses coming back to life
to kill you...
It's impossible.
In hindsight
it was indeed impossible.
It's just that moment
was too real to me.
Perhaps it was just an illusion.
But my comrades did die,
and nearly did Wang and I.
Maybe it was because of the
lack of oxygen
or that you breathed in some toxic gas
that you saw
some unexplainable phenomena?
You know that seeing is not believing.
What you believe to be true
is not determined by your eyes
but your brain.
I know what you mean.
I think that you are pretty
doesn't mean you are physically pretty
but my brain believed that you're pretty...
Right?
What do you want.
I can't leave Wang alone.
You've already quit.
Don't take me wrong.
I'm not gonna go back to the 'business'.
I just wanna get Wang back.
By yourself?
Yeah.
I'm not gonna rob the tomb anyway.
I can do it myself.
I'll be back once I find him.
Don't you worry.
It doesn't matter if you come back or not.
I don't give a shit!
Shirley!
You fucking liar Hu Bayi!!
I knew you!
What you've said has
nothing to do with what you've done!
I'll never trust you anymore!
You fucking arrogant egoistic asshole!
You and Wang Kaixuan together
are nothing but troubles.
Show me
How much trouble you can make!
The long journey
I've been through is still there
And now I am coming back to the start.
Wang Kaixuan is back!
We've been on the horse the whole day,
Man I'm exhausted.
I'm never gonna come to
this god damn shit hole
if not for the dollars.
Watch your mouth.
Hu and I spent our youth here.
Well you brought him,
I didn't.
Screw him
Such a loser who
'can't withstand the sugar-coated bullets.'
Subverted by the female agent of
the American Imperialism in a blink.
This world has changed now
- 'women hold up half the sky.'
or more than half! Look at that chick!
Is this a mining company
or a tomb developing company?
This is sick.
We have rented 200 square miles
of this land
for geological prospecting.
It's all yours.
This
is our President Ms. Ying Caihong.
That's the president?
Some sort Yoga class?
What a company!
Mojin Xiaowei is here.
Cool, isn't it!
Wrong again.
It's rock.
I got too excited
following my instinct.
We were looking for the Goddess Tomb.
But we got the dragon tomb haha.
This is the ninth hole,
are you doing this right?
You should blame Hu Bayi.
Locating has always been his thing.
We would have already
found it if he's here.
It's no use to complain now.
They are gonna blow us instead
if we can't find it.
Ask them not to waste my time.
Fuck.
It's been ages and we still got nothing.
This 'Mojin Xiaowei' is a faker, isn't he.
Hey,young lady
trust me.
'Fen Jin Ding Xue' takes time.
It's a serious job.
Fen jin' means to locate
using ancient compass.
The compass divides into 360 degrees,
24 zones.
Each zone breaks further into five golds,
making a total of 120 golds.
We take all the geological positions
into account...
Speak Chinese.
Speak it in technology terms
If 'Fen jin' is the data,
'Dragon Seeking' would be the programme.
The way the programme works
with the data is 'ding xue'.
Once it's done,
all the tombs in this area will be found.
Do you know what I mean?
Ouch!
What do you want young lady?
Show me your gills.
Yo!
Leave him alone!
From now on,
I will pull one tooth out
every time you get it wrong
till you find get it right.
If there's nothing found by dawn,
I shall execute the breaching of terms.
What breaching of terms?
One hole for each of you.
Grill, is that true?
Ahhhh!
What kind of damn contract is that?
Cheers.
Calm down,
It's just a fuckin tomb...
Ding...
That's it!
There! Must be something!
Drunkard's song in Mongolian
It's nice for you to be here.
But this time we can't afford to have
all of us trapped here.
Or else it's gonna be
the same all over again.
Mojin Xiaowei,
United we stand, divided we fall.
It's what the master told us. I must come.
These people are not regular graverobbers.
I've checked upon this Global Mining Group.
It's more of a cult than a company.
The tomb of Princess Aogu
you mentioned before is
exactly what they are looking for.
Interesting.
She has double identities:
a royal blood and shaman,
worshipped as a Goddess,
The Equinox flower is her instrument.
Legends tell the flower opens the gate
to the underworld.
It brings the dead back to life.
This guy is too drunk to drive.
Don't worry.
The locals are all like this
the more they drink the better they drive.
A little bit more,
I can take you both high up to the sky.
Are you okay?
You drive the car.
Hey bro, let me drive.
Just sit back and relax.
We are almost there.
Almost!
Take the Break!
It's not working!
Make a turn!
Oh my god we are gonna hit the horses.
Let go!
Let it go!
Oh shit...
Hu Bayi!
Forgive me.
Buddha, God, Save me!
It's deep down here,
looks like a it's leading to the tomb
You see see,
Who's the faker hum?!
Mr. Wang, we got it!
Very impressive. Though you've blown
this prairie into the surface of the moon.
Serious business takes time.
Take it easy.
It's no use educating the ignorant.
But the ignorant needs to be educated!
You shouldn't drink and drive...
(Mongolian)
Thank god there's nothing serious.
After you get there,
take off the bridle
and put it on the saddle.
Can the horse find its way back?
Of course.
Thank you.
Cheers,
The Herdsman only has one horse for us
You stay here.
I'll come back after I find Wang.
You do wanna get rid of me huh.
You'll be safe here.
Go to hell. Hu Bayi!
(Mongolian nursery rhyme)
My favorite pony
hides in daddy's horses...
Do you like it?
Shirley
Drag the left rope inwards.
Watch out.
Get out of the way
I'm busy
What are you doing ?
Do you see this?
Don't you think that
our gears are a bit out of time.
Don't just follow your instinct.
We should also follow our times.
We'll see
There tools are inherited
from a thousand years ago,
and have been examined
more than a thousand years.
What the hell do you know?
The air is safe, get prepared.
Boring
Every thing's electronic.
What's the fun of it?!
Hurry up guys!
Okay
What are you doing, Grill? Follow me
You get down there first
Ladies, do think twice.
Raiding a tomb is no joke
Look at you,
are you ready for this?
We all live by beliefs.
How about
I leave you ladies and gentlemen here.
I'm just a business man you know,
Tomb raiding is not my thing.
I'd better stay here.
One two
three
What are you doing?
This is what happens when the
ancient paints react to the air.
Get educated, ignorant!
You see?
See?
This is the difference between
professional and amateur.
By the way, keep an eye on your guys.
From now on
everybody follows my order.
Is this Khitanan?
What does it say?
A blind would see that it says
Tomb raiders shall die.
It is more than a few words
This frescoe must have been
for a thousand years.
We can get at least a cruise
if we trade it in the US.
And some girls too.
Worth getting some kicks.
Wait for me!
You guys over there.
Wow, look at him.
Great pose.
Enough...
This is just a door man.
Is that a dog head?
Don't mess around.
Follow his order.
Master, this bronze badge is
the same with what we had.
No no
This is not a job for little girls
Master
Holy shit, this is...
Keep your hands off
Be quiet.
This corpse has been here for
more than a thousand years
It goes into dust once the wind blows
Stay still.
It's poisonous.
Stay away from them. It's infectious.
Master
Help Me!
Master, help me please!
Let the great awareness
descent upon them,
and the great relief be with them.
Let the great awareness
descent upon them,
and the great relief be with them.
Let the great awareness
descent upon them,
and the great relief be with them.
Yoko
Bastards.
What's wrong?
Hey!
Are you guys deaf?
What did you do?
Tonight is our last chance.
Let's make our aspiration to relieve
all creatures come true.
You are so cruel.
Let the great awareness
descent upon them,
and the great relief be with them.
Keep those nonsense to yourself.
Shut up! The Master is releasing
the souls of the dead from hell.
Take it easy.
You little pussy.
He is still alive
For real.
Grill!Run!
Stay away from them.
Where to?
The first obstacle is, the first...
...whatever.
Wait for me!
We are back here again.
This is a maze.
What poison it is?
It turned them into zombies.
To the other side!
Here again.
Abracadabra.
There you go.
Oi.
You think that you are something?
Fuck you.
Gross!
Mr. Wang,
this must be the legendary weapon
to kill all the zombies.
Hard boiled mule foot.
Mr. Wang. hold it off!
Damn...
Master Kai, this mule foot
might be boiled too much.
The heavenly god overpowers
the tiger on the ground
The holy tower suffocates
the ghost of the river.
Finally.
Go!
Great.
Now we are saved.
Who needs to be saved by him?
Why don't you go back to the capitalists
and drink Coca Cola.
See? They don't need you at all,
and you are dumb enough to go
all the way here only to be scolded.
Let's get out first
then you can bicker
Let's go back from our way in.
Go!
It's over.
We're stuck here.
Surely one of the cave leads to the exit
among all.
There is a statue in each cave.
Goat
Chicken
Dog
Mouse
It's the Zodiac.
No.
Only eight caves.
Not twelve.
It's the eight trigrams of fortune,
the 'Ba Gua'.
What on earth is this place?
We've been running back
and forth for a hundred times.
Every animal represents a diagram.
To seek the Dragon through obstacles,
each obstacle is a gate.
All the obstacles
are made up of the Ba Gua.
The entry is horse. Horse signifies fire.
Mouse,horse, water
fire..goat, earth...dog..
The opposite of northwest is the exit.
Dog is the exit. Come on!
Dog!
Go to hell!
Come on !
Let's go!
Be quick!
I can't go on.
Let's go back and leave this chaos.
Go. Let's go.
Go.
Back. Back where?
I've signed the contract.
You are just a money-grabber,
with no resistance to temptation.
He is the one
Fled to America in your trickery,
and lived a life by cheating on street.
That's what you call quitting.
Now that Mojin Xiaoweis are all here,
as if instructed by god,
you are welcomed to give me your hands.
Hold on there,
young ladies.
Now we've got another case.
I believe you've heard of these two
The great Mr. Hu, Hu Bayi
and Miss Shirley Young.
They are the best of the best.
It's one thing to pay
for Mr. Wang's effort
and it's another to pay for the Mojin team,
which is rare in our business.
Lucky you.
Although,
the cost will go all the way up.
There is too much evil in this world,
and great calamities
will descend upon human.
If you can help me,
the world will be saved.
There were so many killed by you.
ls that what you call saving the world?
Their sacrifices are for
the greater believes.
For you.
For us all.
They are the true believers.
Are you mad?
Madam
Please excuse us.
We three
have washed our hands,
and this is not our thing any more.
You'd better think twice before you act.
Let's go.
Mr Hu,
How much do you want?
Name a price.
Stop acting like Saints.
Petty tomb-raiders.
Say it again?
Tomb-raiders?
You are worse than tomb-raiders.
We are 'bringing the feudalism
down to the ground'
and you?
You are stabbing your people
behind their backs. How glorious you are!
This is Lady Ying Caihong
who's born in the countryside
of Sichuan Province.
A faker huh?
She's said to have a black pupil
and a yellow one
so that she could see
the gods and the ghosts.
Deemed to be an ominous
figure by the villagers,
she was adopted by a tycoon from Japan.
However, it was more than just 'adopted'...
Stop making stories or I'll make you stop!
Miss Yang.
You were said to be
in hospital with illness
once he passed away.
Suddenly reappeared several years later,
you claimed to have obtained
the power to save the world
after discipline yourself in Everest.
Having gone back to Hong Kong,
you created the so called
"Global Holy Disciplinary institution",
whose members are the ones
with fame and fortune
who would pay quite an amount of money.
Please, Shirley.
Dear lady,
Oh no.
Boss Ying.
Please don't take her words seriously.
Young lady likes to know everything
but with her heart of kindness...
We've just got our collaboration going,
Take it easy.
Wang.
What the hell!
You find the tomb of
the Goddess before dawn,
and I'll make him fit as a fiddle.
President,
there is a bridge
Watch out.
Grow up guys.
Find a way and get out.
Yes, or I'll say bye bye to the world.
What on earth did I do to deserve this.
Chairman Mao said,
Be united, not divided.
What's in here? It's so hard.
What are looking at? A person of unity?
Be united, bosses.
Or else we would all die.
Then we shall let them know
who Mojin Xiaoweis really are.
You asshole, I knew
you'd keep the Mojin amulet.
You said you have washed your hands.
You are the one who cheated!
I threw my watch instead
to make you give up
It was the watch I gave you.
Yeah
Nice kick, buddy
You...
Let me do it.
Follow me.
Watch out, Mr. Wang.
Careful.
Come here.
You jerk,
how come you are getting heavier?
Do you ever poop?
Have some pity, sir.
I'm injured only because
I worked too hard for you.
Don't.
Help.
Help!
What bridge is this?
Bridge to the hell, as it seems.
It is the bracelet I gave to you.
It was the watch I gave to you.
The bridge sets fire to
whatever rubs its surface.
It's a material of phosphorus,
with very low ignition point.
The owner of this tomb built the bridge
so that whoever intrudes
would be burned to death.
Are you sure with your decision?
All obstacles are the tests of God,
and we are ready to sacrifice ourselves.
Please don't waste your time,
Mojin Xiaowei,
What does the cracking planks
on the bridge look like?
Split
not split. Split.
The eight trigrams .. Ba Gua!
The planks are in the shape of Ba Gua
In which hides the password.
To seek the Dragon through obstacles,
each obstacle is a gate.
All the obstacles are made up
of the Ba Gua
with Eight directions
leading to life and death and
four phases transforming
from nature to the universe:
Heaven, Thunder, Fire, Mountain
Lake, Wind, Earth, Water.
NW, E, S, NE
W, SE, SW, N
Ba Gua represents the directions.
North west it is.
Please.
We don't need to throw
something ahead first?
This way.
Quick.
This gentleman looks scary. Let's go.
Which way?
South West.
Yoko.
Go to get the last badge.
Give it to me.
Be careful Master.
Dickheads, getting into troubles again !
Now we are turning into fillet steaks.
Run!
Quick!
The fire is breathing down my neck!
Move! Quickly!
It's coming!
Be quick, Mr.Wang.
Quick!
You are gaining weight all the time!
Not the time to complain!
Quick!
I am on fire!
God.
It's not our fault.
There is no way to help them.
Huh!
At this point,
it is better to help ourselves first.
Let's leave!
Go.
Asbestos clothes.
Let's go.
Go.
Take a rest.
We are at minus 7 meters altitude,
northwest 292.3 degree to the mountain.
Southeast to the Yansai Lake
and volcanic crater
Water sound over there.
We can get out if we find
the underground stream.
Go.
Mr. Wang.
Let's go.
What are you waiting for?
The fire to catch you?
What do you mean?
Are you really gonna leave?
We are already here.
I know what's in your mind,
but the past belongs to the past.
We should look forward.
Let's go.
You let things go easily all the time.
I can't.
I do look back.
I love someone and I never let go.
I don't know too much about literature
as you do, Hu. Help me with this.
Please.
Wow,
A poem
of love.
Don't make fun of me.
Would you check it?
To whom?
Whom?
Not telling.
Wang Kaixuan wrote a Love poem!
Are you helping me or not?
Yeah.
Misspellings here
here
and here.
Don't heed it.
E Er Gu Na River, you made a turn.
Turn into my heart
Ok.
I, Hu Bayi, decide to
edit it for you myself.
How about that?
That's my bro.
Is there anything for your bro then?
Who is helping you so much?
The star badge.
No way!
Oi oi.
It fits you.
Ding, I've been resisting
the temptation to ask
if you are willing to sublimate
our innocent comradeship of revolution.
In what way?
My heart started to stammer
when I first saw your bright eyes
Oh
E Er Gu Na River
Your long run have flown
into the mountain of goddess
Idiot!
Flown into the mountain of gods,
into my heart.
Wang Kaixuan,
Stop it please.
People would hear.
I am just reading
what I felt.
Wow, the star of the revolution.
Where did you get it?
A...a friend gave it to me.
Hu... Hu Bayi?
How did you know?
I know Ding liked you more
but I didn't care
I'm willing to do anything for her.
It has been a million times in years
in night time, when I didn't know
if I was awake or not
I saw her face in front of me.
Her looking at me
asking if I've found the Equinox flower
I could not answer.
Don't you forget about her death.
Jump.
Get in.
Hu Bayi, get in.
Be quick.
Ding
Hold on.
Hold on to it.
Don't let go.
We'll all die if we don't cut the wood.
Ding
ding, hold on.
Let go!
No!
Please!
Get back!
What now?
Ding
Jump.
Jump. Ding.
No!
Ding!
Ding died for us.
She really did.
We are finally here.
How can I just take it easy and leave?
Ding sacrificed herself
for you two to be alive.
I really don't understand.
Why do you wanna come back
and die here?
Of course you don't.
I'm ready to give up my life
for Ding any moment.
This is the comradeship of revolution.
Please go ahead if you wanna leave.
Alright.
I go with you for the Equinox flower.
Let them wait for us here.
No joking?
No joking.
I knew that you weren't
an irresponsible man.
Real men
live for loyalty and honesty.
Don't you guys worry about Miss Yang.
I'll take care of her.
Don't worry.
I'll be back soon.
Ciao.
Let's go.
Hu Bayi, you liar.
You two can go to hell.
I never wanna see you guys anymore!
We live the days,
the years by our blood and tear.
We fight against the heaven,
the earth,
the living and the dead.
We are fighting together as a team again.
Yeah. It's fun, isn't it?
What the fuck!
I am sorry bro.
You don't listen to me
and I can only use force.
You son of a bitch.
Are you a real man!
Let me go!
Let go!
You shouldn't have saved me at all.
So that Ding and I could
be together forever
and no need to suffer for living.
Nonsense.
Don't you feel shameful
living a life like this!
Forgetting is betraying
Ding Sitian is already died.
I can't lose you and Shirley.
I have to take you both out of here
for whatever it takes.
Do you understand!
Shut up you traitor!
Damn you!
I've promised Ding
to find Equinox flower.
I meant it.
I'm not like you.
Shirley.
Grill.
Mr. Hu.
Where's Shirley?
I'm useless...
You guys ran pretty fast huh.
Where's Shirley?
Mr. Wang is here.
Hu!
Here you go!
Go!
Damn you!
Little bitch!
Where's Shirley?
Hold!
Don't hurt her. Take your weapons down.
Let's talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
Yuko
Let me go!
Chill.
Take it easy.
Calm down.
Find me the tomb.
Your girlfriend'll be safe.
I'm not his girlfriend!
She is.
What the hell.
Slept together doesn't mean
that we are in a relationship.
Slept together of course means
we are in a relationship.
Slept...slept together?
You...you
You sleep with me everyday.
It's not that complicated
to have a quickie.
No..I mean..What?
When did you do that?
The day we made the vow.
What?
That day?
The day I slept in the toilet
and you two...
Oh my god!
You are such a beast!
Mr. Hu is also a human being.
He didn't take advantage of me.
I fucked him.
Wow you are such a feminist!
Shame!
Shut up!
You idiots!
Fuckin' loser!
Jerks! Wankers! Assholes!
Have you got fuckin' enough
You fuckers!
I don't give a fuckin' shit
about your relationships.
Don't waste my fuckin' time!
Calm down.
Lady.
My compass is broken so I can't
use the 'dragon seeking' now.
The world's going to be destroyed anyway.
I don't mind destroying this one first.
Lady, I have an idea.
I've taken you get out of the traps.
You should trust me.
But I need my girlfriend help me.
Human body could also sense
the electrical currents
To locate the tomb.
It's called Yin-Yang-Gong-Ji.
Here
are eight statues and they're
arranged in a specific way.
They represent Ba Gua.
It seems that we are gonna die...
I'm curious to see how the show goes on
We need to get rid of this rope.
To seek the Dragon through obstacles,
each obstacle is a gate...
You are such a swindler.
Synchronizing the Yin and the Yang...
to form the constellations
for searching the lost dragon...
What are you doing?
Nothing.
What the hell!
You've got strength haven't you!
What? You didn't get hurt by the bullet!
I did I did.
It protected me from the bullet.
No wonder you are heavier!
They've only got one gun.
I distract them, you run!
No you run.
I'm asking you to run!
I'm not leaving you alone here.
Don't don't...
Damn you!
You come here!
Run!
I'm not leaving you.
You son of a bitch.
You lied to me!
Leave!
And rode me as your donkey?!
I'm gonna kill you!
Here's a tunnel!
We are at the bottom of the lake
Shirley, What does it say on the mural?
Heaven opened and Earth cracked.
The very first shaman received
a sacred treasure from the gods.
It has the power to connect Yin and Yang
and to bring the dead back to life.
Princess Aogu obtained it
a thousand years ago.
She named it “The Equinox Flower”.
The “Equinox Flower” blooms every time
the sun and moon unite.
And the gate between life
and death will be open.
Ding said that
The Equinox flower's able to
connect the living and the dead.
You must have came here for this.
Humanity is on the verge of destruction,
this is the last hope.
I'm your only saviour.
If I can get the Equinox flower,
I'll be able to resurrect people
from the death.
Who wants to be saved by a lunatic!
Move!
Calm down.
Let's go.
Ok ok.
That black stone is the Equinox flower?
The mural shows that
it fell directly from the Heaven.
It could be a meteorolite
A meteorolite can save the world?
Be careful.
These three badges are the keys
of the coffin, right?
Yes.
Do what you do best.
Open the coffin!
Mojin Xiaowei,
United we stand,
Divided we fall.
That's it. The 'Mojin' Style!
The Equinox flower!
Mr. Hu!
Mr. Wang!
Miss Shirley!
Shirley.
We've been here before.
Wang,
Look!
Oh my god.
Look at that flag!
It's been twenty years,
we've been in a cycle.
We' re back to the start again...
Boss Hong, I beg you
to save my best friends.
Take back the final payment.
The Mojins can't all die like this!
Screw you!
You little bitch
I'm gonna educate you today!
You said the Equinox Flower
blooms in twilight?
Yes. According to the ancients,
they often refer to Ying Shi,
which is about 5 in the morning...
the incident happened 20 years ago,
what time was it?
I remembered that right
after we escaped from the base,
the sun soon came out.
Do you still remember the light we saw?
It caused the problem.
When the light appeared
The dead soldiers came back to life.
The light was from above.
It must be from the coffin.
No.
The light actually came
from the Equinox flower.
I am saved
The Equinox flower is mine
It is Yin Shi.
We should get out of the palace,
It's dangerous!
Grill!
Let's go, Grill!
Zombies!
They are all Zombies!
Don't eat me!
Run!
Grill!
Master!
Get out of the way!
I don't want you to follow me, get out!
I'm your Slave.
Why do you abandon me?
Save me
Master!
I don't have magic
I only have anesthetics inside my ring,
and a lot of money.
I can't save you
My life is doomed.
There's something growing
inside of my brain. There is no cure.
I need the Equinox flower
I'm dying.
Only with the Equinox flower
I may start a new life.
It's that stone!
Destroy the Equinox flower!
Hu Bayi
Hold onto me, let's go together!
How long are we gonna stay?
As long as we wish.
What's this?
The Equinox flower.
Legends say that
it transcends life and death.
I never knew that it would grow here.
Ding
I always wanted to tell you
I...
We...
The star badge I gave you...
Why is it reversed?
Ding!
Hu Bayi
Do you want the Equinox flower?
You'll never see me if you destroy this.
Are you really going to do this?
You are not Ding Sitian.
You are illusion.
You are not real.
You are my memory,
Dragging me back to the past.
Are you going to forget me?
I won't forget Ding Sitian.
But she sacrificed her own life
Not to leave me in sorrow
but to live in a meaningful life.
Give it to me
Wang
Let go!
Give me the Equinox flower!
The flower belongs to Ding.
No one is allowed to touch it.
I found it!
I found the Equinox flower!
I keep my promise.
From now on,
I will never let anything to hurt you,
even if I die.
Ding.
You were right,
equinox Flower is so beautiful.
Wang Kaixuan
Give it to me
Wang!
This is just an illusion.
It's not real.
The guilty for Ding
is but our obsession.
It's been twenty years,
let go of it
Ding
Bye
Grill!
Zombies! Zombies!
Zombies!
Grill!
Don't follow me!
With the equinox flower
I can come back alive.
The Equinox flower...
I can come back alive
Run! Dangerous!
The palace's self-destructive
Yoko
Wait for me
It's just a meteorolite.
Its light makes people hallucinate.
It doesn't bring the dead back to life.
Shut up
Be careful!
The palace is about to collapse
Hurry up!
Quickly!
Stop following me!
Grill! Hold me tight!
Jump!
The deer is eaten by the tiger,
the tiger is chased by the bear
Mum, Dad, there is a monster in the lake!
Oh my god it looks serious...
We can't get out.
Don't space out.
Think!
Stop!
Coffin!
Coffins float!
We can use them!
Go!
Let's go!
Help!
Master zombies! Please!
Give me!
Please!
Come on!
Hurry up!
It's okay. I'm here.
Shut up, hold tight.
I will beat the hell out of you!
Wanna bite me?
Shut up, hold me!
Go to hell!
I bite the soul out of you!
I think we are on the surface now.
We are still in the underground palace.
We are stuck in the cavern
on the rocky cliff.
Soon we'll be drowned.
A good way to end our lives.
Do you know what I like you the most?
I don't know.
It's the way
you yell at me.
It would be such a pity that
a lovely girl like you to die here with me
Hu Bayi!
Hu Bayi, you asshole!
Let me get out!
You promised that if we die,
we'll die together!
Let me out! Let me out!
We have to die together.
I wanna be with you!
You irresponsible asshole!
No one would ever like such an arrogant
egoistic
smartass punk like you!
I don't want to die with you
I don't want to dream of you
Hu Bayi!
Zombies, don't try to run away!
Come here!
Grill!
Look carefully, look who I am!
I'll beat the hell out of you zombie!
I'm gonna call you papa
if I don't kill you today!
What the hell!
Hu!
Hey you!
You are really swimming into
the depth of hell aren't you!
You dirty lovers!
Where's Hu?
Say something!
Fuck!
You wanna be a hero and live in eternity?
No god damn way!
Get out!
It took me a while down there.
I went to get something.
You bastard!
Are you showing off again?
Liar! Liar! You said that
we would die together!
You are not allowed to
leave me alone from now on.
I'm so useless.
I can't even save my bro...
Your bro is here!
You are alive?
Fuck you!
Alright, something important
needs to be done.
What important business would you have?
You come here and be my witness.
Miss Shirley Yang
Would you like to
subliminate our innocent comradeship
of revolution ?
Are you proposing?
You gotta be kidding me!
Who's ever proposed in a coffin?
My treasure!
Hey!
It's real gold!
Give me back!
I'm gonna make a fortune!
Young Lady...
How dare you!
That was a good one!
Grill you bastard!
Or shall we leave it till
we get back to America.
Are you a real man?
You two are shameless!
Mr. Hu.
Miss Yang.
What the hell are you doing ?
Wang Kaixuan
Mr. Wang here we go again.
Good timing.
I thought I would
never see you guys again
Are we alive or are we dead?
Are we in Heaven or are we in Hell?
Whatever you wish!